President Kimura-san
기무라상 사장
President Kimura, what are you looking for?
기무라 회장님, 무엇을 찾고 계시나요?
The corpse was untouched.
시체는 손대지 않았습니다.
Why do you cut open the wound?
상처를 왜 베나요?
what
무엇
I do not know
모르겠어요
Where has the stuff gone?
그 물건은 어디로 갔나요?
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I do not know
모르겠어요
lie
거짓말하다
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
I'm not lying
나는 거짓말을 하고 있지 않다
Why don't you guys believe me?
너희들은 왜 나를 믿지 않는거야?
What are you guys?
너희들은 무엇인가?
There aren't any.
아무것도 없습니다.
Who else is there?
또 누구 있어요?
Did I say it wrong?
내가 잘못 말했나요?
No, there's no one else.
아니, 다른 사람은 없어요.
I'll tell you.
내가 말해주지.
If you dare to lie
감히 거짓말을 한다면
I'll shoot you to death.
나는 당신을 쏴 죽일 것입니다.
Mr. Kimura-san
Mr. Kimura-san
I'm not lying.
나는 거짓말을 하지 않습니다.
I really didn't lie.
나는 정말로 거짓말을 하지 않았다.
There is one person
한 사람이 있습니다
Speak up.
발언.
There is only one person.
사람은 단 한 명뿐입니다.
I'm a patient.
나는 환자입니다.
I'm just leaving for a moment.
나는 잠시 동안 떠날 예정이다.
I thought he was a normal patient.
나는 그가 평범한 환자인 줄 알았다.
I didn't think that when I found the magpie's corpse,
까치 시체를 발견했을 때는 그런 생각은 못했어요.
Suddenly she brought a sword to threaten me.
갑자기 그녀는 나를 위협하기 위해 칼을 가져왔습니다.
forced me to ask
나한테 물어보라고 강요했어
What did you bring and ask?
무엇을 가지고 와서 물어보셨나요?
She asked what items were hidden in Xi Qi's corpse.
그녀는 Xi Qi의 시체에 어떤 물건이 숨겨져 있는지 물었습니다.
Am I the one who took it?
내가 가져간 사람인가?
I didn't take it.
나는 그것을 받아들이지 않았습니다.
Where are you
어디세요
It's here.
여기 있어요.
Where?
어디?
In the room inside
안쪽 방에는
inner room
안방
Chief Kimura
기무라 수석
I didn't mean to hide it just now.
지금은 숨기려고 한 게 아니었어요.
That's what I mean.
그게 내 뜻이야.
You know.
알잖아.
It's you.
당신이에요.
Zuo Shuang Tao
주오솽타오
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
Do you know this woman?
이 여자를 아시나요?
His name is Zuo Shuangtao.
그의 이름은 Zuo Shuangtao입니다.
Chief Kimura
기무라 수석
Just now holding this knife
지금 이 칼을 들고
come threaten me
와서 나를 위협해
my war dagger
나의 전쟁 단검
America gives special military command
미국이 특별 군사 지휘권을 부여하다
Are you the army commander?
당신은 육군 사령관입니까?
Please accept it.
그것을 받아들이십시오.
Have you come to investigate the magpie?
까치를 조사하러 오셨나요?
yes
예
Not bad
나쁘지 않다
You are very brave.
당신은 매우 용감합니다.
Then I ask, where is Xi Que's recipe?
그럼 Xi Que의 요리법은 어디에 있습니까?
I can't find it
찾을 수가 없어요
Are you the one who opened the door?
문을 열어준 사람이 당신인가요?
I cut it out myself
내가 직접 잘라냈어
But I can't find the formula.
하지만 공식을 찾을 수 없습니다.
lie
거짓말하다
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
He definitely wasn't lying.
그는 확실히 거짓말을 한 것이 아니었습니다.
If you lie
거짓말을 하면
He wouldn't have used that knife to threaten me.
그는 나를 위협하기 위해 그 칼을 사용하지 않았을 것입니다.
What do you think?
어떻게 생각하나요?
Even though I can't find the formula
비록 공식을 찾지는 못했지만
But it was unexpectedly profitable.
그런데 예상외로 수익이 났다.
Kijinzankimura
Kijinzankimura
Today I know there is no way to go.
오늘 나는 갈 길이 없다는 것을 압니다.
But I will not tell you a single word.
그러나 나는 당신에게 한 마디도 말하지 않을 것입니다.
I'm warning you to avoid this.
나는 이것을 피하라고 경고하고 있습니다.
You'd better kill me.
나를 죽이는 게 좋을 것 같아요.
You misunderstood me.
당신은 나를 오해했습니다.
I'm not interested in killing people.
나는 사람을 죽이는 것에는 관심이 없습니다.
Not interesting
흥미롭지 않음
not beautiful
아름답지 않다
Doctor Chiao
치아오 박사
Do you know what my dream is?
내 꿈이 뭔지 알아?
Probably not you
아마 당신은 아닐 거예요
my dream
내 꿈
I want to be a doctor.
나는 의사가 되고 싶다.
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
What field of doctor do you want to be?
당신은 어떤 분야의 의사가 되고 싶나요?
surgeon
외과 의사
Main surgeon
주치의
Very good
매우 좋은
Do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
I started having this dream.
나는 이런 꿈을 꾸기 시작했다.
Since when did you have this dream?
언제부터 이런 꿈을 꾸셨나요?
How am I supposed to know this?
내가 이걸 어떻게 알겠어요?
When I was in elementary school
내가 초등학교 다닐 때
There was a time when I was studying biology.
생물학을 공부하던 시절이 있었습니다.
Dissecting a frog
개구리 해부
It's a little frog that still jumps around.
아직도 뛰어다니는 작은 개구리입니다.
cute little frog
귀여운 개구리
I'll use a nail.
못을 사용하겠습니다.
Then he took his four claws and nailed them to a piece of wood.
그런 다음 그는 네 개의 발톱을 가져다가 나무 조각에 못을 박았습니다.
Then he used a blade to cut open his belly.
그런 다음 그는 칼을 사용하여 배를 열었습니다.
Then slowly remove the belly.
그런 다음 천천히 배를 제거하십시오.
The nerves inside are twitching.
내부의 신경이 경련을 일으키고 있습니다.
Hands and feet twitching like crazy.
손과 발이 미친 듯이 꿈틀거린다.
Nothing can stop it.
아무것도 그것을 막을 수 없습니다.
My curiosity and enthusiasm for biological sciences
생명과학에 대한 나의 호기심과 열정
Have you achieved my dream?
내 꿈을 이루셨나요?
How can I help you?
어떻게 도와 드릴까요?
Very easy
아주 쉽게
Look.
바라보다.
Now we have
이제 우리는
Examples of anatomy of a living person
살아있는 사람의 해부학적 예
Chief Kimura
기무라 수석
Here you will say
여기서 당신은 말할 것입니다
you
너
Go get the clothes the doctor put on me.
가서 의사가 입힌 옷을 가져오세요.
The clothes the doctor wears
의사가 입는 옷
and surgical equipment as well
수술장비도 그렇고
Hurry, hurry.
빨리 빨리.
good
좋은
I'm going myself.
나는 스스로 갈 것이다.
Tell me.
말해 주세요.
What is your mission?
당신의 임무는 무엇입니까?
I said it.
내가 말했어.
Where is the boss?
사장님은 어디 계시나요?
How many people are there in your organization?
귀하의 조직에는 몇 명이 있습니까?
Where do you move?
어디로 이사하시나요?
I said it.
내가 말했어.
You say it.
당신은 그것을 말한다.
I listen
내가 듣고
I just want to say
나는 단지 말하고 싶다
While in this room
이 방에 있는 동안
It's just someone who is bound.
그저 묶여 있는 사람일 뿐입니다.
They are Chinese people who do not resist at all.
그들은 전혀 저항하지 않는 중국인입니다.
But outside this room
하지만 이 방 밖에서는
On every road
모든 길에서
In many households
많은 가정에서
in shanghai
상하이에서
at the head of the dong
동장에서
in china
중국에서
There are still many friends of ours.
우리 친구들은 아직도 많이 있어요.
They will record your crimes.
그들은 당신의 범죄를 기록할 것입니다.
Their hearts were filled with anger and anger.
그들의 마음은 분노와 분노로 가득 차 있었습니다.
They had weapons clenched tightly.
그들은 무기를 꽉 쥐고 있었습니다.
They will fight until the last minute.
그들은 마지막 순간까지 싸울 것이다.
Thousands and thousands of Chinese people
수만 명의 중국인이
They will all die under my sword.
그들은 모두 내 칼 아래서 죽을 것이다.
including you
당신을 포함하여
is just one of them
그 중 하나일 뿐이야
but
하지만
I will let you die
나는 당신을 죽게 내버려 둘 것이다
very beautiful
매우 아름다운
Very beautiful death
정말 아름다운 죽음
What the hell is she doing to her?
대체 그녀가 그녀에게 무슨 짓을 하는 걸까요?
It's bad.
그것은 나쁜.
this evening
오늘 저녁
You must have an important mission.
중요한 사명을 가지고 있어야 합니다.
I definitely had to go see that doctor at Shi'an Hospital.
나는 반드시 시안병원에 있는 그 의사를 만나러 가야만 했다.
Never mind.
괜찮아요.
I'd rather not go see President Kimura.
나는 기무라 회장을 만나러 가지 않는 편이 낫다.
Probably afraid of harsh words again.
아마도 또다시 거친 말을 두려워하게 될 것입니다.
cannot
할 수 없다
I can't go
나는 갈 수 없다
If I go
만약 내가 간다면
In the future, there will definitely be no chance of meeting Mr. Kijin.
앞으로도 기진씨를 만날 기회는 절대 없을 것입니다.
Whatever I say, I have to go.
무슨 말을 해도 난 가야 해요.
Anyway, I have to go.
어쨌든 나는 가야 해.
No matter how I force myself, I have to go.
아무리 억지로라도 가야 해요.
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
I'm the backup knife man.
나는 백업 칼맨이다.
Today I came to see you.
오늘은 당신을 만나러 왔습니다.
May I have some advice?
조언을 좀 드려도 될까요?
It was Xiao Gao.
샤오가오였습니다.
no
아니요
The story of Wutian Xinxuan
Wutian Xinxuan의 이야기
I heard that you are going to take Xiao.
당신이 샤오를 데리고 간다고 들었습니다.
Take Zhao Wutian Xinxuan away.
Zhao Wutian Xinxuan을 데려가십시오.
We are very happy.
우리는 매우 행복하다.
Meaning
의미
We took good care of Wutian Xinxuan.
우리는 Wutian Xinxuan을 잘 돌보았습니다.
Why am I talking about this?
내가 왜 이것에 대해 이야기하고 있습니까?
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
My meaning is
내 뜻은
Would you rather I raise your horse?
차라리 말을 키우시겠습니까?
You don't have to worry.
걱정할 필요가 없습니다.
I will take care of you like my real child.
진짜 내 아이처럼 돌봐줄게요.
Why is my mouth so stupid?
내 입이 왜 이렇게 멍청한 걸까?
I'm just leaving for a moment.
나는 잠시 동안 떠날 예정이다.
I thought he was a normal patient.
나는 그가 평범한 환자인 줄 알았다.
I didn't think that when I found the magpie's corpse,
까치 시체를 발견했을 때는 그런 생각은 못했어요.
Suddenly she brought a sword to threaten me.
갑자기 그녀는 나를 위협하기 위해 칼을 가져왔습니다.
Still forced to ask me again
아직도 나에게 다시 물어볼 수밖에 없다
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
What are you asking?
뭘 물어 보는 거냐?
She asked what items were hidden in Xi Qi's corpse.
그녀는 Xi Qi의 시체에 어떤 물건이 숨겨져 있는지 물었습니다.
Am I the one who took it?
내가 가져간 사람인가?
I didn't take it.
나는 그것을 받아들이지 않았습니다.
Where are you
어디세요
It's here.
여기 있어요.
Where?
어디?
I'm in the room.
나는 방에 있습니다.
cannot
할 수 없다
I can't say this yet.
나는 아직 이것을 말할 수 없습니다.
I'm willing to tone it down like this.
저는 이렇게 톤을 낮춰볼 의향이 있습니다.
It's easy to get rejected.
거절당하기 쉽습니다.
My second-in-command is a person of good deeds.
나의 부사령관은 선한 일을 하는 사람이다.
There doesn't seem to be any virtue.
별 메리트가 없을 것 같습니다.
cannot
할 수 없다
I need to think a bit.
좀 생각해볼 필요가 있어요.
elder sibling
형
Go get the clothes the doctor put on me.
가서 의사가 입힌 옷을 가져오세요.
The clothes the doctor wears
의사가 입는 옷
And then
그런 다음
surgical equipment as well
수술장비도 그렇고
Hurry, hurry.
빨리 빨리.
good
좋은
let me go
나를 보내줘
Japanese people are perverted.
일본인들은 변태적이다.
Even if you don't apply.
신청하지 않더라도.
There's no need to perform an autopsy on your body alive.
살아 있는 몸을 부검할 필요는 없습니다.
Chen surname
첸 성
You did this to Zuo Shuangtao.
당신은 Zuo Shuangtao에게 이런 짓을 했습니다.
Don't you know he's my wife?
그 사람이 내 아내인 걸 모르시나요?
Guo Guo
궈궈
I've come.
내가 왔어.
You don't have to be afraid.
두려워할 필요가 없습니다.
Don't be afraid.
두려워하지 마십시오.
It'll open soon.
곧 열릴 거예요.
You don't have to be afraid.
두려워할 필요가 없습니다.
I've come.
내가 왔어.
I'm here
나는 여기 있다
Don't be afraid.
두려워하지 마십시오.
You listen to me.
당신은 내 말을 들어요.
Now is not the time to cry.
지금은 울 때가 아니다.
Do you understand?
이해했나요?
The two of us must hurry and get out of here.
우리 둘은 서둘러 여기서 나가야 해.
Do you understand yet?
아직 이해하셨나요?
Look at me.
날 봐.
Let's go.
갑시다.
we go
우리는 간다
go
가다
walk slowly
천천히 걷기
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
From today onwards
오늘부터
you are me
당신은 나야
Spitting.
침을 뱉습니다.
What are you talking about me?
나에 대해 무슨 말을하는거야?
sincere
진실된
no problem
괜찮아요
Let's say it like this.
이렇게 말해보자.
This time there was definitely no problem.
이번에는 확실히 문제가 없었습니다.
Why do you have to use secondary skills here?
여기서 왜 보조스킬을 사용해야 하나요?
It's a long story.
이건 긴 이야기다.
But don't let him know that we
하지만 그에게 우리가 있다는 사실을 알리지 마세요
I feel sorry for him a little too much.
나는 그에게 조금 너무 안타까움을 느낀다.
Chief Kimura
기무라 수석
President Kimura-san
기무라상 사장
I'm in already.
난 이미 들어왔어.
He's gone in.
그는 들어갔다.
What should I do?
어떻게 해야 하나요?
I don't care about him anymore.
나는 더 이상 그 사람에 대해 신경 쓰지 않습니다.
However, he didn't know who had done it.
그러나 그는 누가 그런 짓을 했는지는 몰랐습니다.
Is that okay?
괜찮나요?
Sorry, I'm a bit late.
죄송합니다. 조금 늦었습니다.
And what about Doctor Qiao?
Qiao 박사는 어떻습니까?
Stay behind me.
내 뒤에있어.
Don't look.
보지 마세요.
He's dead.
그는 죽었어.
So strange.
정말 이상해요.
What about my scalpel?
내 메스는 어쩌지?
Are you here?
여기 계세요?
Should have died already
이미 죽었어야 했는데
It's bad.
그것은 나쁜.
Why?
왜?
My scarf fell inside.
내 스카프가 안으로 떨어졌어요.
Every day I wear it to the bank.
매일 나는 그것을 입고 은행에 갑니다.
He'll definitely remember.
그 사람은 분명히 기억할 거예요.
Where did you fall?
어디로 떨어졌나요?
on the table
책상 위에
This is not true.
이것은 사실이 아닙니다.
I must be blindsided.
나는 눈이 멀었음에 틀림없다.
Hallucinations
환각
Saw all the hallucinations
환각을 다 봤어
It must have been because I used my brain too much just now.
지금은 내가 뇌를 너무 많이 썼기 때문이겠지.
I saw a hallucination.
나는 환각을 보았다.
Why is he sitting in front of the door?
그 사람은 왜 문 앞에 앉아 있는 걸까요?
It's a person.
사람이에요.
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
I'd like to sit here first.
나는 먼저 여기 앉고 싶습니다.
After a while, I'll go back.
잠시 후 다시 돌아오겠습니다.
Everything became normal again.
모든 것이 다시 정상이 되었습니다.
Why is there a knife in your hand?
손에 칼은 왜 들고 있는 걸까요?
Lieutenant Chen
첸 중위
Why did you get it?
왜 얻었나요?
I'm him.
나는 그 사람이다.
What's wrong with you?
왜 그래?
To be so afraid
너무 두려워서
What is it about him?
그 사람에 대한 내용은 무엇입니까?
Secondary weapon
보조무기
Do you want me to work?
내가 일하길 바라나요?
When performing your duties, speak quickly.
직무를 수행할 때에는 신속하게 말하십시오.
I'm not going in anymore.
나는 더 이상 들어가지 않을 것이다.
It's so scary.
너무 무섭다.
Chief Kimura
기무라 수석
Kimura
Kimura
this
이것
What happened here?
여기 뭔 일 있었 니?
Why did Captain Kimura die?
기무라 선장은 왜 죽었는가?
I understand.
이해합니다.
You are a criminal who kills people.
당신은 사람을 죽이는 범죄자입니다.
no
아니요
you watch
당신은 시청
Cut corners sharply
모서리를 날카롭게 자르세요
The relationship was cut off.
관계가 끊어졌습니다.
The partition wall was smooth.
칸막이벽은 매끄러웠다.
And there were no abrasions on his forehead.
그리고 이마에는 찰과상도 없었습니다.
Plus there are abrasions on the skin.
게다가 피부에 찰과상도 있습니다.
Second knife
두 번째 칼
Captain Kimura's wound was caused by a sharp knife.
기무라 선장은 날카로운 칼에 상처를 입었습니다.
The weapon is the scalpel in your hand just now.
무기는 지금 손에 들고 있는 메스입니다.
There must have been blood stains on the knife.
칼에 핏자국이 있었나 봐요.
It is easy to prove whether it is Mr. Kimura's or not.
기무라 씨의 것인지 아닌지는 쉽게 증명할 수 있습니다.
The most important thing is
가장 중요한 것은
There's your fingerprint on that knife.
그 칼에 당신 지문이 있어요.
Now there is complete evidence and witnesses.
이제 완전한 증거와 증인이 있습니다.
Are you still making excuses for me?
아직도 나한테 변명하는 거야?
Boss Chen
첸 보스
Why do you slander people like this?
왜 이렇게 사람을 비방하는 걸까요?
I just picked up this knife here.
방금 여기에서 이 칼을 집어들었습니다.
Two handles
손잡이 2개
I heard that President Kimura
기무라 회장님이 그러셨다고 들었습니다.
During this time I want to take away the horse you raised.
이 시간 동안 나는 당신이 키운 말을 빼앗고 싶습니다.
There are many thoughts in your heart.
마음속에는 많은 생각이 있습니다.
You will say that there is resentment in your heart.
당신은 마음속에 원한이 있다고 말할 것입니다.
This is your motivation for killing people.
이것이 사람을 죽이는 동기입니다.
Boss Chen
첸 보스
Nuts are very important to me.
견과류는 나에게 매우 중요합니다.
But I wouldn't kill anyone for it.
그러나 나는 그것을 위해 누구도 죽이지 않을 것입니다.
I don't want to doubt you.
나는 당신을 의심하고 싶지 않습니다.
After all, we are colleagues.
결국 우리는 동료입니다.
But what method do I have?
그런데 나에겐 어떤 방법이 있나요?
You appear on the scene.
당신이 현장에 등장합니다.
use weapons in hand
손에 있는 무기를 사용하다
Most importantly, you have a motive for killing people.
가장 중요한 것은 사람을 죽이려는 동기가 있다는 것입니다.
How can you keep me from doubting you?
내가 당신을 의심하지 않게 하려면 어떻게 해야 합니까?
I'm used to being second-back.
나는 세컨드백에 익숙하다.
I
나
but
하지만
But this mistake is really big.
그런데 이 실수는 정말 크다.
I can't carry it anymore.
더 이상 가지고 다닐 수가 없어요.
Er, this one.
어, 이거요.
Is this your fault?
이게 당신 잘못인가요?
Go with me to Sararup HQ.
나와 함께 사라럽 본부로 가세요.
Got there.
거기에 도착.
There is a reasonable explanation.
합리적인 설명이 있습니다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Someone has arrived.
누군가 도착했습니다.
There are people
사람들이있다
Go.
가다.
Boss Chen
첸 보스
I don't want anyone to know.
나는 누구에게도 알리고 싶지 않습니다.
I dodge
나는 피한다
Can't bear it.
견딜 수 없습니다.
The first pot in the world
세계 최초의 냄비
I really can't bear it.
정말 견딜 수가 없어요.
Hallucinations
환각
Hallucination again
다시 환각
I'm not afraid
나는 두렵지 않다
Bodhisattva protection
보살 수호
May God protect you too.
신께서 당신도 보호해 주시기를 바랍니다.
Lieutenant Chen
첸 중위
you are the same
너도 똑같아
You're not even in front of me.
당신은 내 앞에도 없습니다.
Do you have a feeling?
느낌이 있나요?
Do you have a feeling? That's a hallucination.
느낌이 있나요? 그것은 환각입니다.
sit up
일어나
Look.
바라보다.
You didn't forget, right?
잊지 않았죠?
You've made a big mistake.
당신은 큰 실수를 저질렀습니다.
Do you know?
당신은 알고 있나요?
Boss Chen
첸 보스
I didn't actually kill Chief Kimura.
나는 실제로 기무라 대장을 죽인 것이 아니다.
yes
예
Maybe it's really not you.
어쩌면 정말 당신이 아닐 수도 있습니다.
Then you really killed him.
그럼 당신은 정말 그를 죽였군요.
What if you are possessed by a vengeful spirit?
복수심에 사로잡혀 있다면 어떻게 될까요?
That day when he dragged the corpse
시체를 끌고 가던 날
I've already told you.
나는 이미 당신에게 말했습니다.
This way, you will often be possessed by a vengeful spirit.
이런 식으로 당신은 종종 복수심에 사로잡히게 될 것입니다.
Or am I really possessed?
아니면 내가 정말 홀린 걸까?
Hey, friend.
야, 친구 야.
When you faint
기절할 때
Originally, I had planned to call the S Communications Headquarters.
원래는 S커뮤니케이션즈 본사에 전화하려고 했는데요.
Let them come and catch people.
그들이 와서 사람들을 잡게 해주세요.
I picked up the phone
나는 전화를 집어 들었다.
Then I suddenly thought of
그러다 문득 생각난게
For many years we have been doing business.
수년 동안 우리는 사업을 해왔습니다.
Even though
일지라도
You are Zhao An's subordinate.
당신은 Zhao An의 부하입니다.
But normally
하지만 평소에는
This doesn't cause me much distress.
이것은 나에게 큰 괴로움을 주지 않습니다.
Is that right?
그렇죠?
And then most importantly
그리고 가장 중요한 것은
I think you
난 당신을 생각
Not a bad person
나쁜 사람은 아니야
So I hung up the phone.
그래서 전화를 끊었어요.
I just can't stand it.
나는 참을 수 없습니다.
At least we used to be colleagues.
적어도 우리는 동료였어.
Is that right?
그렇죠?
I thought I would help my friend.
친구를 도와야겠다고 생각했어요.
Take this matter.
이 문제를 생각해 보세요.
Never mind.
괜찮아요.
friend
친구
It's like this.
이렇습니다.
I, myself, can only help with this.
나 자신은 이 일에만 도움을 줄 수 있습니다.
Because today you are Japanese.
오늘 당신은 일본인이기 때문입니다.
So if Japanese people meet them
그러니 일본 사람들이 그들을 만나면
I'm in danger too.
나도 위험해요.
I can't help you anymore.
나는 더 이상 당신을 도울 수 없습니다.
I'll go first.
내가 먼저 갈게.
You find your own way.
당신은 자신의 길을 찾습니다.
Lieutenant Chen
첸 중위
You must help me.
당신이 나를 도와주어야 합니다.
Think of a way to help me.
나를 도울 방법을 생각해 보세요.
Lieutenant Chen
첸 중위
I'm begging you.
부탁드립니다.
Whatever you say, I will obey you.
당신이 무슨 말을 하든 나는 당신의 말을 따르겠습니다.
can?
할 수 있다?
Boss Chen
첸 보스
Get up
일어나
You bully me for being soft-hearted.
당신은 마음이 약하다고 나를 괴롭히는군요.
I'll tell you.
내가 말해주지.
Let me think first.
먼저 생각해 보겠습니다.
Let me think about it.
생각 좀하자.
Hurry and tell me.
어서 말해주세요.
How did you get to the hospital?
병원에는 어떻게 가셨나요?
Originally, today I wanted to go to Saraming Headquarters.
원래 오늘은 사람이 본부로 가려고 했는데요.
Chief Kimura
기무라 수석
Please don't take the beans with you.
콩을 가지고 가지 마세요.
Waited at the door for a long time.
오랫동안 문 앞에서 기다렸습니다.
It wasn't easy for Chief Kimura to come out.
기무라 과장이 나오기는 쉽지 않았다.
I didn't know how to say it.
나는 그것을 어떻게 말해야할지 몰랐습니다.
Wait for me to breathe quickly
빨리 숨 쉴 때까지 기다려요
Chief Kimura's car has already been driven.
기무라 추장의 차는 이미 운전을 해본 상태다.
So I chased after his car.
그래서 나는 그의 차를 쫓아갔습니다.
Then he ran to the front door of Shi'an Hospital.
그리고는 시안병원 정문으로 달려갔다.
I saw President Kimura enter the cardiology department.
기무라 회장이 심장내과에 들어가는 모습을 봤다.
After hesitating many times
여러 번 망설인 끝에
I finally thought of something to say.
드디어 할 말이 생각났습니다.
I'm going to see President Kimura.
기무라 회장님을 만나러 가겠습니다.
Wait for me to push the door out.
내가 문을 밀어낼 때까지 기다리세요.
Saw someone outside first.
밖에서 누군가를 먼저 봤어.
I'm afraid.
나는 두려워한다.
shouted Chief Kimura.
기무라 대장이 소리쳤다.
But no one answered.
그러나 아무도 대답하지 않았습니다.
Do I think something might happen?
무슨 일이 일어날 것 같나요?
In my heart I'm afraid
마음속으로는 두려워
I saw a scalpel in the room.
나는 방에서 메스를 보았다.
So I want to keep it to protect myself.
그래서 나 자신을 보호하기 위해 보관하고 싶습니다.
you know
알잖아
I raised Xiao Gao myself.
나는 Xiao Gao를 직접 키웠다.
I was afraid that my two swords would pierce it.
내 두 개의 검이 그것을 뚫을 까봐 두려웠다.
I didn't dare take my sword with me.
나는 감히 칼을 가져갈 수가 없었다.
The story after this
이 이후의 이야기
Do you know it all?
다 알고 계시나요?
I say friend
친구라고 해
You have done inappropriate things over and over again.
당신은 부적절한 일을 반복해서 했습니다.
That is, pick up that knife.
즉, 그 칼을 집으십시오.
Really naive
정말 순진해
Let me think about what to do first.
먼저 무엇을 해야 할지 생각해 보겠습니다.
Look.
바라보다.
one two three
하나 둘 셋
three corpses
시체 세 개
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
No need to recommend much.
많이 추천할 필요는 없습니다.
Is that right?
그렇죠?
This doctor
이 의사
He is a doctor who specializes in heart disease.
그는 심장병을 전문으로 하는 의사이다.
But he still has one more person who is.
하지만 그에게는 아직 한 사람이 더 남아있습니다.
is Captain Kimura's spy.
기무라 선장의 스파이입니다.
Is that a spy?
저 사람이 스파이인가요?
How do you know?
어떻게 알 수 있나요?
I'll tell you something.
내가 말해주지.
Lucky you found me
운 좋게도 당신이 나를 찾았어요
Think about how you would thank me.
나에게 어떻게 감사할지 생각해 보세요.
Is it an arrest warrant?
체포 영장인가요?
I found it on that doctor's desk.
그 의사 책상에서 그걸 발견했어요.
You try looking at this picture.
이 사진을 보세요.
Then you slowly turn around and look at this person.
그러다가 천천히 돌아서서 이 사람을 바라봅니다.
This code is magpie.
이 코드는 까치입니다.
Isn't that the corpse that's sitting?
저거 앉아 있는 시체 아닌가요?
yes
예
friend
친구
The person who died today was Jian Shan of Kimura Village.
오늘 사망한 사람은 기무라촌의 지안샨(Jian Shan)이었습니다.
Kimura Kenzan
Kimura Kenzan
If the command department finds out
사령부에서 알게 된 경우
That's a big deal, you know?
그거 큰일이야, 알지?
so
그래서
So we must
그래서 우리는
You must use your hands to move at the scene.
현장에서 이동하려면 손을 사용해야 합니다.
to the people of the military headquarters
군 본부 사람들에게
I think the story is like this.
이야기는 이 정도인 것 같아요.
good
좋은
Xi Que
시퀘
Stir repeatedly
반복해서 저어주세요
But he has heart disease.
하지만 그 사람은 심장병을 앓고 있어요.
So he came to the hospital.
그래서 그는 병원에 왔습니다.
So the heart department had the doctor prescribe medicine.
그래서 심장과에서는 의사에게 약을 처방하게 했습니다.
But he didn't think that
하지만 그 사람은 그렇게 생각하지 않았어
This doctor is a spy for Lord Kimura.
이 의사는 기무라 경의 스파이입니다.
He remembered the criminal.
그는 범인을 기억했습니다.
Therefore, he found an opportunity to inform Chief Kimura.
그래서 기무라 서장에게 알릴 기회를 찾았다.
When the doctor tried to stabilize the magpie
의사가 까치를 안정시키려고 했을 때
then injected into the solution
그런 다음 용액에 주입
I don't know what to put in it.
무엇을 넣어야할지 모르겠습니다.
Probably because of an overdose of drugs.
아마도 약물 과다 복용 때문일 것입니다.
causing his unexpected death.
그의 예상치 못한 죽음을 초래했습니다.
younger brother
남동생
These things are difficult to explain.
이런 것들은 설명하기 어렵습니다.
But from now on, you'll have to listen carefully.
하지만 이제부터는 잘 들어야 합니다.
Do you understand yet?
아직 이해하셨나요?
Because Kijinzankimura was about to go on stage.
왜냐하면 키진잔키무라가 무대에 오르려고 했기 때문이죠.
After Lord Kimura came
기무라님이 오신 후
I saw Xi Que.
나는 Xi Qu를 보았다.
Already dead
이미 죽었어
but on him
하지만 그에게
Couldn't find the information he wanted.
그가 원하는 정보를 찾을 수 없었습니다.
So he thought he was a doctor.
그래서 그는 자신이 의사라고 생각했습니다.
Stealing his information
그의 정보를 훔치는 것
Pulled out a gun and was angry and wanted to kill that guy.
총을 꺼내들고 화가 나서 그 사람을 죽이고 싶었어요.
But what about the doctor?
하지만 의사는 어떻습니까?
Protect it first.
먼저 보호하세요.
He hid a scalpel in his sleeve.
그는 소매에 메스를 숨겼습니다.
I need to find a scalpel.
메스를 찾아야 해요.
At the same time, President Kimura picked up a gun and had to shoot.
그와 동시에 기무라 회장은 총을 집어들고 총격을 가해야 했다.
The doctor scratched Lord Kimura's arm.
의사는 기무라 경의 팔을 긁었다.
What will you do?
당신은 무엇을 할 것인가?
this is my hand
이건 내 손이야
You hit the kli on the roof of the wooden village.
당신은 나무마을 옥상에서 클리를 쳤습니다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
The doctor then seized the opportunity when Lord Takeshimura wasn't expecting it.
의사는 다케시무라 경이 예상하지 못했을 때 기회를 포착했습니다.
Then he stabbed an unsuspecting bystander in the neck with a single knife.
그런 다음 그는 칼 하나로 의심하지 않는 구경꾼의 목을 찔렀습니다.
But Commander Kimura
하지만 기무라 사령관은
It is Zhong Zhuo of the Japanese Empire.
일본제국의 종주오입니다.
Why was it so easily picked up?
왜 이렇게 쉽게 뽑힌 걸까요?
so
그래서
Captain Kimura endures severe pain.
기무라 선장은 심한 고통을 겪는다.
and fight with the doctor
의사랑 싸우기도 하고
Brother, from now on
형님 이제부터
Come hit the bed here.
여기 침대에 누워보세요.
not enough
부족한
good
좋은
last
마지막
Kimura-san
Kimura-san
He fought over the scalpel that the doctor had.
그는 의사가 가지고 있던 메스를 놓고 싸웠습니다.
The doctor died instantly.
의사는 즉시 사망했습니다.
Chief Kimura lost too much blood.
기무라 대장은 피를 너무 많이 흘렸습니다.
Finally, it was poured into a pool of blood.
마침내 그것은 피 웅덩이에 부어졌습니다.
and both die
그리고 둘 다 죽는다
friend
친구
I
나
There's probably only this way.
아마 이 방법밖에 없을 것 같아요.
Boss Chen
첸 보스
Thank you very much today.
오늘 정말 감사드립니다.
Otherwise I probably would.
그렇지 않으면 아마 그럴 것입니다.
It's not.
그렇지 않습니다.
I suddenly remembered.
문득 생각났어요.
Why are you here?
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
I came to pick up medicine.
약을 사러 왔어요.
It's this late.
이렇게 늦었구나
It's this late and I came to get medicine.
시간이 너무 늦어 약을 받으러 왔어요.
My wife has a fever
아내가 열이 나네요
I'll go get some medicine.
약 좀 사러 갈게요.
Then you take the medicine.
그럼 약을 드세요.
So why are you running here?
그럼 왜 여기서 뛰고 있는 걸까요?
You think I want to come to the scene here.
내가 여기 현장에 오고 싶다고 생각하는군요.
You think I want to see this happen?
내가 이런 일이 일어나는 걸 보고 싶을 것 같아?
I saw you sneaking around the door.
당신이 문밖으로 몰래 돌아다니는 걸 봤어요.
I want to come and see
꼭 와보고 싶어요
What exactly are you doing?
정확히 무슨 일을 하고 있나요?
Were you at the scene too?
당신도 현장에 있었나요?
Why do people doubt me?
사람들은 왜 나를 의심하는 걸까요?
No.
아니요.
Why must you stare at me like this?
왜 나를 이렇게 쳐다보아야 하는 걸까요?
Now I'm helping you.
이제 나는 당신을 돕고 있습니다.
Plus, you have a motive for killing people.
게다가 사람을 죽이려는 동기도 있습니다.
There's your fingerprint on it.
거기에 당신의 지문이 있습니다.
Has Boss Chen forgotten?
첸 상사는 잊었나요?
Just now when the scene was set
방금 장면이 설정되었을 때
I'm using a pad here.
저는 여기서 패드를 사용하고 있어요.
yes
예
So you forgot?
그래서 잊었나요?
This knife was taken from this cart.
이 칼은 이 카트에서 가져온 것입니다.
That handle of yours
너의 그 손잡이
It's here with me.
그것은 나와 함께 여기에 있습니다.
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
Boss Chen
첸 보스
this is you
이것은 당신입니다
What's wrong with me?
나에게 뭐가 문제 니?
What's the matter?
무슨 일이야?
You are my benefactor.
당신은 나의 은인입니다.
my real parents
나의 진짜 부모님
Just remember that.
그거만 기억하세요.
Boss Chen
첸 보스
From now on
지금부터
We will be in the same boat.
우리는 같은 배를 타게 될 것입니다.
no
아니요
You have to think clearly.
명확하게 생각해야합니다.
I am a person on a boat
나는 배를 탄 사람이다
As for you, you are the one who is about to drown.
곧 익사할 사람은 바로 당신입니다.
You're just lucky.
당신은 단지 운이 좋은 것뿐입니다.
Hold on to my ship
내 배를 붙잡아라
Just begging me to save your life.
당신의 생명을 구해달라고 간청할 뿐입니다.
Do you understand?
이해했나요?
but
하지만
I could always kick you off the boat.
난 언제든지 당신을 배에서 쫓아낼 수 있어요.
There's more.
더있다.
I'll tell you something, old man.
내가 하나 말해주지, 늙은이.
Me helping you isn't free.
내가 당신을 돕는 것은 공짜가 아닙니다.
From now on
지금부터
On the surface, you were still Zhao An's subordinate.
표면적으로 당신은 여전히 ​​조안의 부하였습니다.
But the truth worked for me.
그러나 진실은 나에게 도움이 되었습니다.
What do I have you do next?
다음에는 무엇을 하라고 합니까?
You just have to do it.
당신은 그것을해야합니다.
But you don't ask me.
하지만 당신은 나에게 묻지 않습니다.
Why do you do this?
왜 이런 일을 하는가?
You mustn't tell anyone else.
다른 사람에게 말하면 안 됩니다.
What have I commanded you to do?
내가 너희에게 무엇을 하라고 명령했느냐?
Do you understand?
이해했나요?
understand
이해하다
If you still don't understand even a little bit.
아직도 조금이라도 이해가 되지 않는다면.
So this knife
그럼 이 칼은
Appear in the evidence room
증거실에 나타나다
in the evidence room
증거실에서
Then Chief Chen
그럼 첸 실장님
So from now on
그럼 지금부터
Are you going to make me do something bad?
나한테 나쁜 짓을 하게 만들 셈이냐?
friend
친구
Good story or bad story?
좋은 이야기인가, 나쁜 이야기인가?
Later you will know.
나중에 알게 될 것입니다.
Let's go.
갑시다.
I will go with you
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것이다
Why did you follow me?
왜 나를 따라왔나요?
Have you finished work?
일을 마쳤나요?
Then go back.
그럼 돌아가세요.
I've finished decorating the place, haven't I?
나는 장소 장식을 끝냈지, 그렇지?
What are you decorating?
무엇을 꾸미고 있나요?
If something goes wrong
뭔가 잘못되면
Are there any footprints here?
여기에 발자국이 있나요?
Are there any other footprints?
다른 발자국은 없나요?
Didn't think of that?
그 생각은 안 해보셨나요?
You must redecorate.
새롭게 꾸미셔야 합니다.
As I said, isn't it?
내가 말했듯이 그렇지 않습니까?
I'll tell you.
내가 말해주지.
It's only for the military headquarters.
군 본부에만 해당됩니다.
no loopholes
허점이 없다
The case is closed.
사건은 종료되었습니다.
You will be safe, do you understand?
당신은 안전할 거예요, 알겠어요?
understand
이해하다
That is,
그건,
So I'm alone.
그래서 나는 혼자입니다.
Until when do I have to do it?
언제까지 해야 하나요?
Whatever you want to do, just do it.
당신이 하고 싶은 것이 무엇이든, 그냥 하세요.
Well, I'll tell you.
글쎄, 내가 말해주지.
6 a.m.
오전 6시
The cleaners come and clean themselves.
청소부가 와서 스스로 청소를 합니다.
Lieutenant Chen can relax.
첸 중위는 편히 쉬세요.
Turn your volume down a bit.
볼륨을 조금 낮추세요.
Wrapped around my two handles
내 두 손잡이를 감싸서
Come back nicely.
잘 돌아오세요.
Is it better?
더 나은가요?
Tell me honestly
솔직하게 말해봐
What exactly is the group?
정확히 어떤 그룹인가요?
Didn't I say that before?
내가 전에 그렇게 말하지 않았나요?
Blood Spirit Group
혈령그룹
Youth patriotic organization
청년애국단체
Zuo Shuangtao, are you still lying to me?
Zuo Shuangtao, 아직도 나에게 거짓말을 하고 있나요?
I was at the door, hearing it clearly.
나는 문 앞에 있었고 그 소리를 분명히 들었습니다.
You have already admitted that you are the commander of the army.
당신은 이미 군대의 사령관임을 인정했습니다.
Are you really the commander of the army?
당신이 정말 군대의 사령관입니까?
You've heard it all, haven't you?
다들 들어보셨죠?
Why are you still asking me?
왜 아직도 나한테 묻는 거야?
A real military uniform.
진짜 군복이네요.
I can't think of it at all.
나는 그것을 전혀 생각할 수 없다.
that
저것
The Chen family's wife never expected to be the leader of the army.
첸 가문의 아내는 군대의 지도자가 될 것이라고는 전혀 예상하지 못했습니다.
Many years ago
몇 년 전
I'm careful
조심해요
Be careful with your words and actions.
말과 행동을 조심하세요.
I'm wary of setting out on a ten-thousand-year-old ship.
만년된 배를 타고 출발하는 것은 조심스럽습니다.
But now I don't think so.
하지만 지금은 그렇게 생각하지 않습니다.
I'm just a boat full of dynamite.
나는 단지 다이너마이트로 가득 찬 배일 뿐입니다.
So what do you plan to do?
그래서 당신은 무엇을 할 계획입니까?
Complain to me
나에게 불평하다
mean person
못된 사람
I complain to you
나는 당신에게 불평합니다
If I want to complain to you
내가 당신에게 불평하고 싶다면
So why should I help you?
그러면 내가 왜 당신을 도와야 합니까?
I complain to you
나는 당신에게 불평합니다
But just now, when you massacred Mu
그런데 지금 네가 Mu를 학살했을 때
Even if it's in our military system
우리 군사체계에 있다고 해도
It is a first-class skill.
일등 스킬입니다.
Where did you come to study?
어디서 공부하셨나요?
When combined with everything else
다른 모든 것과 결합하면
But I don't believe it.
그러나 나는 그것을 믿지 않습니다.
You are just a traitor.
당신은 단지 배신자입니다.
Or are you just a lurker?
아니면 그냥 잠복꾼인가요?
belongs to another line
다른 라인에 속해 있어요
or
또는
Press conference
기자 회견
Now I'm asking you:
이제 나는 당신에게 묻고 있습니다 :
Why did you turn around?
왜 돌아섰나요?
Why did you come to ask me?
왜 나한테 물어보러 왔어?
Tell me the truth.
나에게 진실을 말해.
What exactly is your purpose in going to the hospital?
병원에 가는 목적이 정확히 무엇입니까?
What's the mission?
임무는 무엇입니까?
You think I'm going to tell you my mission?
내가 너한테 내 임무를 말할 거라고 생각하는 거야?
You think I want to know?
내가 알고 싶어할 것 같아?
What is your work?
당신의 일은 무엇입니까?
Knowing what good it will have for me
그것이 나에게 어떤 유익이 될지 아는 것
I also help you
나도 당신을 도와요
I do it for myself.
나는 나 자신을 위해 그것을한다.
Do you know who I killed today?
오늘 내가 누구를 죽였는지 아세요?
Kimura Kenzan
Kimura Kenzan
Head of the Intelligence Unit of the Military Police Command
헌병사령부 정보부장
yes
예
Now I
지금
This time I threatened another pawn.
이번에는 다른 폰을 위협했습니다.
Is it right?
맞아?
at the scene
현장에서
and causing doctors to kill each other
의사들끼리 서로 죽이게 만들고
But what if I make a mistake?
하지만 실수하면 어쩌지?
What if I didn't expect anything?
아무것도 기대하지 않았다면 어떻게 되나요?
Aren't we both finished playing?
우리 둘 다 놀기 끝난 거 아냐?
Where is it?
어디입니까?
That's someone from the military headquarters.
군 본부에서 나온 사람이에요.
The Sharing Headquarters was not in a position to find fault with this.
나눔본부는 이에 대해 비난할 입장이 아니다.
So I told you that Zuo Shuangtao
그래서 내가 Zuo Shuangtao라고 말했어요.
You must tell me.
당신이 나에게 말해야합니다.
You must tell all the circumstances of the job.
직업의 모든 상황을 말해야합니다.
This is how I thought of it.
나는 이렇게 생각했다.
How will I face it next?
앞으로는 어떻게 대처할 것인가?
We are going to face this no matter what.
우리는 무슨 일이 있어도 이 문제에 직면할 것입니다.
Speak quickly.
빨리 말하세요.
My duty is
내 의무는
Investigate the traitor who once hid in the army.
한때 군대에 숨어 있던 반역자를 조사하세요.
that concealed a certain Yan
특정 Yan을 숨긴 것
What is the purpose of investigating magpies?
까치를 조사하는 목적은 무엇입니까?
He stole the Sullian paper recipe.
그는 설리안 종이 제조법을 훔쳤습니다.
Is that a formula?
그게 공식인가요?
Have you received the medicine formula yet?
아직 약 처방을 받지 못하셨나요?
do not have
이 없습니다
Zuo Shuang Tao
주오솽타오
Do you still have something to hide from me?
아직도 나한테 숨길 게 남아있나요?
I'll tell you.
내가 말해주지.
If you don't tell the truth again
다시는 진실을 말하지 않으면
Both of us will be stuck with reality.
우리 둘 다 현실에 갇혀있을 것입니다.
I'm not lying
나는 거짓말을 하고 있지 않다
I suspect that Xi Que hid this medicinal formula in the wound.
나는 Xi Que가 상처에 이 약을 숨겼을 것이라고 의심합니다.
So I used the dagger to cut it.
그래서 단검을 사용해 잘라냈습니다.
But I can't find it
하지만 찾을 수가 없어요
But I found a piece of tissue paper.
그런데 휴지 한 장을 발견했어요.
This proves that my decision was not wrong.
이것은 내 결정이 틀리지 않았다는 것을 증명합니다.
only
오직
Someone must have picked it up before.
누군가가 전에 그것을 주웠을 것입니다.
has been taken away
빼앗겼어
So it's because of the magpie.
그러니까 까치 때문이에요.
Have you given the medicine formula to someone?
누군가에게 약을 준 적이 있습니까?
Zuo Shuang Tao
주오솽타오
You still haven't told me the truth, have you?
당신은 아직도 나에게 진실을 말하지 않았죠?
I'll tell you
내가 말해줄게
I am not interested
관심 없어
I don't care in the slightest.
나는 조금도 상관하지 않습니다.
Perhaps the exchange has already been completed.
아마도 교환이 이미 완료되었을 수도 있습니다.
What's the exchange?
교환은 무엇입니까?
Chongqing sent people to negotiate with Xi Qi.
충칭은 Xi Qi와 협상하기 위해 사람들을 보냈습니다.
Thinking of spending a lot of money to buy that formula?
그 분유를 사기 위해 많은 돈을 쓸 생각이신가요?
Chongqing
충칭
Chongqing, why use a paper formula made from coins?
충칭, 왜 동전으로 만든 종이 제조법을 사용하나요?
They want to counterfeit coins.
그들은 위조 동전을 원합니다.
Destroying the economy and finances of border areas
국경지역의 경제와 재정을 파괴한다
But when it's finished
하지만 그것이 끝나면
Why did you still send me to look for the magpie?
왜 아직도 까치를 찾으라고 나를 보내셨나요?
They thought of getting rid of Xi Que before exchanging.
그들은 교환하기 전에 Xi Que를 제거하려고 생각했습니다.
and take the formula back
그리고 공식을 다시 가져오세요
But their previous actions had failed.
그러나 그들의 이전 행동은 실패했습니다.
My superior ordered the mission to be halted.
내 상사는 임무를 중단하라고 명령했다.
Hasn't it stopped completely?
완전히 멈춘거 아냐?
So what are you doing today?
그래서 오늘 뭐 할거야?
Zuo Shuang Tao
주오솽타오
I decided to disobey orders.
나는 명령에 불복종하기로 결정했습니다.
I had to get the medicine formula back first.
먼저 약을 돌려받아야 했어요.
traitor
배신자
You're a traitor.
당신은 배신자입니다.
You are clearly the actions of a rebel organization.
당신은 분명히 반군 조직의 행동입니다.
I know
알아요
But do you know?
하지만 당신은 알고 있나요?
counterfeit coins
위조 동전
is to destroy the anti-Japanese plot
반일 음모를 파괴하는 것입니다
It's because of disrespect.
무례함 때문이에요.
that opposes the sacrifice of the Japanese people
일본 국민의 희생을 반대하는
okay
좋아요
Zuo Shuang Tao
주오솽타오
You are not only a spy in the royal court.
당신은 궁정의 스파이일 뿐만이 아닙니다.
You still sympathize.
당신은 여전히 ​​​​동정합니다.
and also supports the Communist Party
또한 공산당을 지지한다.
Do you know what this is called?
이것을 뭐라고 부르는지 아시나요?
The penalty is doubled.
벌금이 두 배로 늘어납니다.
How do you support CCP?
CCP를 어떻게 지원합니까?
I began to feel
나는 느끼기 시작했다
Perhaps the CCP's ideas and beliefs
아마도 중국 공산당의 사상과 신념은
It is the right way for China's future.
이것이 중국의 미래를 위한 올바른 길이다.
What are you talking about so far?
지금까지 무슨 얘기를 하고 있는 걸까요?
If it's true
그것이 사실이라면
I dare say
내가 단언하는데
Okay.
좋아요.
I don't want to listen anymore.
더 이상 듣고 싶지 않아요.
-You don't have to talk about these things with me.-Don't.
- 이런 얘기는 나한테 할 필요 없어요.- 그러지 마세요.
The clues you said
당신이 말한 단서는
I remember it all.
나는 그것을 모두 기억합니다.
Let me think carefully first.
먼저 곰곰히 생각해 보겠습니다.
Think carefully.
잘 생각 해봐.
See what flaws there are.
어떤 결함이 있는지 확인하세요.
Hurry and sleep.
빨리 자.
One more thing, I'll tell you.
한 가지 더 말씀드리겠습니다.
Tomorrow the two of us will go to work.
내일 우리 둘은 출근할 거예요.
You have to act like you don't see anything happening.
아무 일도 일어나지 않는 것처럼 행동해야 합니다.
Everything is normal.
모든 것이 정상입니다.
wait a minute
잠깐 기다려요
Is there something wrong?
뭔가 문제가 있나요?
What are you going to do?
당신은 무엇을 할 예정입니까?
Today I'm here to help you.
오늘 나는 당신을 돕기 위해 왔습니다.
You can't kill me.
당신은 나를 죽일 수 없습니다.
I am
그래요
I am a traitor
나는 배신자다
But I didn't do anything bad.
하지만 나는 나쁜 짓을 하지 않았습니다.
What I'm talking to you about today
오늘 내가 당신에게 말하는 내용은 무엇입니까?
If you dare to say even one word
감히 한 마디라도 한다면
I don't speak
나는 말하지 않는다
You trust me.
당신은 나를 신뢰합니다.
I definitely won't tell.
나는 확실히 말하지 않을 것입니다.
I definitely won't tell anyone.
나는 아무에게도 말하지 않을 것입니다.
I'm not kidding.
농담이 아냐.
I'll tell you.
내가 말해주지.
This type of dagger used by US soldiers
미군이 사용하는 단검의 종류
There are four handles at home.
집에는 손잡이가 4개 있습니다.
There is also a Blanning M 1935 pistol.
Blanning M 1935 권총도 있습니다.
One Curtin pistol
커틴 권총 1개
who had to assassinate the foreign minister instead of Chen Zhu
Chen Zhu 대신 외무부 장관을 암살해야 했던 사람
must use it
그것을 사용해야 한다
There are still three US Army MK grenades.
아직 미 육군 MK 수류탄이 3개 있습니다.
a bottle of cyanide
청산가리 한 병
Poisoning of the 5th Japanese Guangzhou Navy team.
일본 광저우 해군 제5팀의 독살.
It caused the death of 19 people like that.
그렇게 19명이 사망했다.
Don't.
하지 않다.
Okay.
좋아요.
I
나
I don't want to know about these things.
나는 이런 것들에 대해 알고 싶지 않습니다.
I'm the one who helped you, I'm in the middle of my wits.
당신을 도와준 사람은 나인데 정신이 없군요.
Because I love you
나는 당신을 사랑하기 때문에
What am I?
난 무엇인가?
You trust me.
당신은 나를 신뢰합니다.
okay
좋아요
can
~할 수 있다
Come here.
이리 오세요.
Why do I go in?
내가 왜 들어가요?
sleep together
같이 자다
Why do we have to sleep together?
왜 우리는 같이 자야 하는 걸까요?
Husband and wife don't sleep together?
남편과 아내는 함께 자지 않습니까?
Not at this time.
지금은 아닙니다.
Aren't you sleeping separately?
따로 자는 거 아냐?
Today you helped me
오늘은 당신이 나를 도와줬어요
I have forgiven you.
나는 당신을 용서했습니다.
do not
하지 마라
come
오다
no
아니요
Kua kua kua kua kua kua kua kua kua kua
그랬어요, 그랬어요, 그랬어요, 그랬어요, 그랬어요, 그랬어요
You wouldn't have taken advantage of me while I was asleep.
내가 자고 있는 동안 당신은 나를 이용하지 않았을 겁니다.
When I sleep
내가 잠을 잘 때
Jiaping
자핑
If I really died today
만약 내가 오늘 정말로 죽는다면
will you miss me
날 그리워 할 거니
Think about it.
생각해 보세요.
I thought for a long time.
나는 오랫동안 생각했다.
Because of that
그것 덕분에
Even if you do it for me
네가 나를 위해서 그런 짓을 해도
Take good care of yourself.
자신을 잘 돌보세요.
look after yourself
너 자신을 돌봐
If we're to blame, blame the era we're living in right now.
비난을 해야 한다면 지금 우리가 살고 있는 시대를 비난하라.
Blame the Japanese
일본인을 비난하라
Why must there be a war?
왜 전쟁이 일어나야 합니까?
I remember you said just now
방금 네가 말한 걸 기억해
CCP beliefs and ideas
중국 공산당의 신념과 사상
Even if it is the future of China
그것이 중국의 미래라 할지라도
Are you serious?
진심인가요?
Actually
실제로
I secretly read Lao Lu's investigation report.
나는 라오루의 조사 보고서를 몰래 읽었다.
I found their beliefs
나는 그들의 신념을 찾았습니다
To have power
힘을 가지려면
There is hope.
희망이 있습니다.
They were willing to die and not give up.
그들은 기꺼이 죽고 포기하지 않았습니다.
A couple worthy of admiration
존경할 만한 커플
We must live a good life.
우리는 좋은 삶을 살아야 합니다.
I just want to be alive.
나는 단지 살아있고 싶다.
Even if there is hope
희망이 있어도
Promise me
약속해줘
I will not do anything wrong to the Chinese people.
나는 중국인에게 나쁜 짓을 하지 않을 것이다.
I will remember
나는 기억할 것이다
Are you sure that person is a magpie?
저 사람이 까치인 게 확실해요?
Most definitely.
가장 확실합니다.
I have ordered you to stop your mission.
나는 당신에게 임무를 중단하라고 명령했습니다.
Why do you have to stalk him?
왜 그를 스토킹해야합니까?
I don't want to let it go easily.
쉽게 놔두고 싶지 않아요.
Because you don't want to give up easily, right?
쉽게 포기하고 싶지 않으니까요?
There is no other motivation.
다른 동기는 없습니다.